hotcelebshome.com 2013-12-24

# Contact Us : Hot Celebs Home

Contact Information: Send us a [E-mail](mailto:hotcelebs@gmail.com) or a message on [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/hotcelebshome).

## Claims of Infringement

All images and text copyright to their owners and used under the fair use copyright law, section 107. All images and text are thought to be public domain and found through various free sources on the internet and publications. **Please contact us with any legal problems and we’ll be happy to remove any thing in breach.**

“Sec. 107. – Limitations on exclusive rights: Fair use 

“Notwithstanding the provisions of sections 106 and 106A, the fair use of a copyrighted work, including such use by reproduction in copies or phonorecords or by any other means specified by that section, for purposes such as criticism, comment, news reporting, teaching (including multiple copies for classroom use), scholarship, or research, is not an infringement of copyright.”

## Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site www.hotcelebshome.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. 

www.hotcelebshome.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense (including their [partners](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149&ctx=sibling)), CPX interactive, Blogads, Adify. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: hotcelebs@gmail.com

**Third Party Advertiser Cookies and Web Beacons**  
This web site participates in Six Apart Media, a comprehensive advertising program provided by Six Apart Ltd. for publishers all across the Web. This section of our privacy policy describes how Six Apart Ltd. and the third party advertising networks and advertisers that display advertisements through Six Apart Media (collectively, “Advertisers”) collect, use, store and disclose data from visitors to this Web site.

A “cookie” is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies can be used to target advertisements relevant to your interests, based on your visits to different Web sites, to provide traffic measurement and other analytics and to conduct research. 

A “Web beacon” is an electronic file on a Web page that allows a Web site to count users who have visited that page, to access certain cookies and to provide auditing, research and reporting for advertisers. 

When your browser requests a page that displays advertising from one of the Advertisers, the Advertiser may view, edit or set its own cookie through your browser. In addition, the Advertiser may place its own Web beacon in the page, which may be triggered by your browser’s request.

Advertiser Privacy Policies

If you would like to contact the Advertisers to learn more about their privacy policies and what options (if any) they offer to opt out of their data collection and use, please follow these links to their Web sites:

Six Apart Ltd.  

Six Apart Media third party advertising networks and advertisers  
<http://www.sixapart.com/advertising/solutions-for-bloggers/privacy/3rd-party-list/index.html>

Some of these third party advertising networks are participants in the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. You can learn more about NAI and how you may “opt out” of targeted advertising delivered by NAI member ad networks [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
